

Data Scientist & Python Programmer

## **About Me**

Hello! I'm Hossein Mohseni. I'm a 22 years old student of software engineering who started programming one year before going to university with language C++. But after going to university I started Python programming and now I am a skilled python programmer. I am passionate about Data Science and ML. Beside being a programmer, I have some activities on music, especially on metal and rock. I am also a content creator on Youtube in my free time.

Age 23

Email mohseni.h1999 [at] gmail [dot] com

Location Arak, Iran

## **Main Skills**

Python	
Data Science	
NLP & Text-Mining	
HTML, CSS	
Django	

#### **Other Skills**

FL Studio

**Android Programming** 

UI/UX Design

Music Knowledge

**Electric Guitar Playing** 

Graphic Design

# **Work Experience**

# Data Scientist and Python Development at Roupel DataWare Co.

Jan 2020 - Present

I started my work in Roupel Company since Jan 2020, but actually I was not a Data Scientist at first. After April 2020, my main focus is on data science and I am constantly studying and practicing in this field.

## Graphic Designer (Self-Employed)

Apr 2017 - Jan 2021

Graphic designing was my first career in life. But after a while, I realized that I was not very interested in graphic design and it is boring for me. So I stopped working on graphic design. I am currently doing personal designs for fun.

# UI/UX Designer (Self-Employed)

Nov 2019 - Sep 2020

## **Education**

Bachelor Of Computer Software Engineering from Arak University

2018 - Present

Science and Mathematics from National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (Sampad)

2014 - 2017

# Languages

Persian (Native) English (Professional)

#### **Intrests**

Video Games Music

## **Contact**

**Address** 

Arak, Iran

**Email** 

mohseni.h1999 [at] gmail [dot] com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohsenihossein

(iii) /hosseinhimself

? /hosseinmh1

**♦** /hosseinmoh

/hosseinhimself